question_data = [{
    "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the "
                 "movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace "
                 "founder Tom Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Shaquille O&#039;Neal appeared in the 1997 film &quot;Space Jam&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor "
                 "who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]



















    # {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
    #          "you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, "
    #          "you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
